Guide to the Brian Lassiter Hip Hop Collection, circa 1980-2013.
Lassiter, Brian Hip Hop Collection
- Series III. Publicity and Advertising
  - Magazines, Newsletters, and Photos
    - Inferno Magazine Promotional Materials, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Grip Media Kit, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Karma - 4th Annual Ludacris Foundation Benefit Dinner Booklet, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Loose Photographs, Undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
      Mainly undated, includes studio, band, and retail store shots. Also includes a photo of M. Shabazz with Run DMC in 1987.
  - Movies and Television
    - Ogana Records Inc. Project Proposal, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Powerplay Entertainment, LLC Memorandum, May 1, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - "Murder on McLemore Avenue" Information and Script, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - "Black Gangster" Script, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Movie Idea Pitch to Brian Lassiter, August 2001 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - "Game Over", 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      Marketing materials including photocopy of F.E.D.S. Magazine Vol. 1 Issue #4
    - "Treat 'Em Right", 2002 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Hi-Tech Media Movie Works, 2003-2004; CD-2664 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - "Decisions" Part I Script by Mark D. Williams, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Cooking with Hip-Hop, July 2007 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Investment Packets and Marketing Plans
    - Round the Globe Music, Pyramid Group, February 1994, April 1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - World Won Records Materials, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Miami-Ft. Lauderdale Interconnect Media Kit, February 2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - HitMeOff.com, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Rebellious Entertainment, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - The Pinnacle Entertainment Group, Inc., undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - The J. Hines Company, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - StarLight Media Kit, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Loose Posters and Flyers
    - Box of postcard-sized flyers and street hand-outs for various artists (Box 8)
    - Posters (Box 9)
    - Posters (Folder 1)
- Series IV. Media
  - CDs and DVDs
    - Shady, 2001; CD-2500 (Box 2)
      Executive Producer Big "C", Music Produced by "Idol Hands", South Paw Records
    - Shady, 2001; CD-2501 (Box 2)
    - Elle Gie feat. Bobby Nick: iBarnie Rubble, 2009; CD-2502 (Box 2)
      Suthern Flava Records
    - Elle Gie feat. Bobby Nick: iBarnie Rubble, 2009; CD-2503 (Box 2)
    - Trigg da Kidd, undated; CD-2504 (Box 2)
      T.o.m.G (Take over Music Group)
    - "U Know" and "Never Change" from the forthcoming album Grind Mode, undated; CD-2505 (Box 2)
      Mega Buck$ Radio, Bezzle Inc.
    - Zoe Pound: "Little Haiti Stories", undated; CD-2506 (Box 2)
      Most Wanted Records
    - Hurra-Season: Hatin, undated; CD-2507 (Box 2)
      Crunchtime Music Label
    - Soundmaster "T" & Playa face Joker, undated; CD-2508 (Box 2)
      One Nation Entertainment & Fasheezy Entertainment
    - The Architect: "I Build Beats", 2004; CD-2509 (Box 2)
      Rhymes Over Matter Pub.
    - Soni D's Urbanmix: Show # 99-27, Hour 1, undated; CD-2510 (Box 2)
    - 'King of Detroit', undated; DVD-1500 (Box 2)
      D.W.I. Records
    - Power Move: Love inside, undated; DVD-1501 (Box 2)
      For Playgirl Video
    - Reel 2005 Cut Close Productions, 2005; DVD-1502 (Box 2)
  - Cassette Tapes
    - The Jihad volume 1/Man, Woman, and Child/Sun, Moon, Stars, undated; tr-10778 (Box 2)
      Executive Producer Harlen "Face" Akins, Produced by Zula Da Cosmic Overseer for No Room for Squarez Productions, Dig it Records
    - Hi-Life Tracks, undated; tr-10780 (Box 2)
      Executive Producer Harlen "Face" Akins, Produced by Brian Hood for Hi Life Productions, Dig it Records
    - Rejected Mindstate/"A message from Blakey" (revisited), undated; tr-10781 (Box 2)
    - Hi Life Songs Volume 1, undated; tr-10782 (Box 2)
  - VHS Videos
    - Parts Unknown: "Mental Journey", 1995; V-9006 (Box 2)
      mAd Scientist Prod.; TRT 11:00
    - The Lunasicc: "Hard times", September 10, 1997; V-9007 (Box 2)
      AWOL Records; TRT 4:14
    - Sammy Sam: Ridin' Wit Some Playas, March 30, 1999; V-9008 (Box 2)
      Director Dwayne B. Perryman III; Producer Mala Perna; Big Oomp Records/Platinum Entertainment; Moonsoon Films; TRT 4:00
    - OVADO$E: "Make That Thang Clap", August 17, 2001; V-9009 (Box 2)
      Directors Dr. Teeth and Bobby Yan; Producers Tracey Davis & Obassi Teah; Editor Karl Slater; Heavyweight Pictures; Zillionaire Records; TRT 4:22
    - Ill Beingz: "Milkshake", June 4, 2002; V-9010 (Box 2)
      Director Andre Wilkins; Foundation Entertainment; TRT 4:28
    - Big C: "Hell is a Flame", 2003; V-9011 (Box 2)
      Southpaw Records; TRT 4:56
    - Zoe Pound: "Comin' For You" from album "Little Haiti Stories", undated; V-9012 (Box 2)
      Director R. Malcolm Jones; Most Wanted Records
    - Zoe Pound: "Comin' For You" (Commercial), undated; V-9070 (Box 2)
      Most Wanted Records RT: :30
    - Rnation.com Episode #11, undated; V-9013 (Box 2)
      Guest: Raggs; Artist: OL Head Slang Bangaz
    - Uncle Al + 2-Minicanos "Menealo", undated; V-9014 (Box 2)
      Intervideo Duplication, Inc.; On Top Records, Corp.
    - Boyd Records/Slim Goodie: "Cold as Ice" Commercial, undated; V-9015 (Box 2)
    - Big Tabb: "Raw Dawg", undated; V-9016 (Box 2)
      Rags to Riches Entertainment
    - Mr. Freeze 12th Anniversary Party, undated; V-9017 (Box 2)
    - From Jumpstreet, undated; V-9068 (Box 2)
      1. Minstrels and Stage 2. Blues to Jazz 3. Soul 4. Recording Industry 5. R&B
    - New York City Breakers at the Kennedy Center, Washington D.C., undated; V-9069 (Box 2)
    - The Graveyards "Lonely Seed", 1996; V-9071 (Box 2)
      Shantell Records. RT: 4:28
    - "Ice or Life", undated; V-9072 (Box 2)
      Featuring a live performance and release party of the new maxi single "Killa Like Me". A Mody Mod Film.
- Series V. Lassiter Hip-Hop and Music Related Magazines and Periodicals Collection
  - Booklets
    - Kai's Power Tools 3: Macintosh/Power Macintosh/Windows NT/Windows 95 Explorer's Guide, 1995 (Box 2)
      by Steven Frank
    - Bob Marley, 1994 (Box 2)
      Chris Welch
    - Essential Egypt (The Essential Travel Guide Series), 1990 (Box 2)
      by Nina Nelson
    - The Message of Islam, 1976 (Box 2)
      Abdullah Yusaf Ali
    - Blue Note: The Jazz Photographs of Francis Wolff: A Book of Postcards, 1992 (Box 2)
    - The Blues: A Book of Postcards, 1989 (Box 2)
      photographs by Stephen C. LaVere
    - In Full Effect: A Positive Rapper's Revenge, 1995 (Box 2)
      by Ahmed Karim Muhammad
  - Magazines and other periodicals, 1979-2015
    - Titles A-H
      - 3XS: Savvy Sexy Successful Lifestyle, 2003-11-2004-03 (Box 56)
      - Access Atlanta, 2004-09-02-2007-04-01 (Box 56)
        September 2-12, 2004; October 7-17, 2004; April 14-24, 2005; March 22 - April 1, 2007
        Published by the Atlanta Journal-Constitution
      - Ace Entertainment, 2013-02 (Box 43)
      - African Americans On Wheels, 1998 (Box 43)
        Vol. 3 Issue 4
      - African Quest, The, Winter 1998 (Box 56)
        Issue 5
      - American Band, The, 1985-03 (Box 43)
      - American Film, 1989-07-1989-08 (Box 43)
      - American Visions: Maryland's African American Culture, 1994 (Box 43)
      - Amricas, 1985-09-1985-10 (Box 43)
        Vol. 37 No. 5
      - Art Papers, 2005-07-2005-08 (Box 43)
      - Asis, 2008 (Box 43)
        Issue 7
      - Atlanta 1996: Guide to the 1996 Olympic Games, 1996 (Box 43)
      - Atlanta Black Business Monthly, The, 1994-03 (Box 43)
      - Atlanta Business Chronicle, 2000-06-23-2000-06-29 (Box 43)
        Vol. 23 No. 3
      - Atlanta Business Journal, Summer 2005, Winter 2007 (Box 43)
        Vol. 13 No. 3, Vol. 15 No. 1
      - Atlanta Events, 1987-07-1987-09 (Box 64)
        Vol. 28; Vol. 31
      - Atlanta Fever, 2003 (Box 43)
      - Atlanta Goodlife, 2000-01-2000-07 (Box 56)
        Vol. 1 No. 8
      - Atlanta Intown, 2015-06 (Box 56)
        Vol. 21, no. 6
      - Atlanta Journal, The, 1989-09-05 (Box 56)
        Vol. 107, No. 135
      - Atlanta Journal-Constitution, The (Box 56)
        Personal Business Section; Arts and Books Section; Final Edition, Advertising Supplement; The Big A: The Atlanta-Journal Constitution Ultimate Guide
      - Atlanta Link Up, 1999-01-1999-07 (Box 64)
        Vol. 1 No. 1, 4, 6-7
      - Atlanta Now (Box 43)
      - Atlanta Regional Music Directory, 1984-1995 (Box 64)
        1984-1985, 1993, 1995
      - Atlanta Sports and Fitness (Box 43)
      - Atlanta Star Report, 1988-03-14-1996-03 (Box 63)
        Vol. 1, No. 8; Vol. 1, No. 9; Vol. 1, No. 11; Vol. 1, No. 17; Vol. 2, No. 13; Vol. 3, No. 1; Vol. 5, No. 3
        Begins as "Atlanta Star Record Pool"
      - Atlanta Star Report (large format), 1994-01-1995-08 (Box 56)
        Vol. II Issue 1-4, 6, 8, 9, 12; Vol. III Issue 1, 3-9
      - Atlanta Tribune (The Magazine), 2015-03-2015-06-15 (Box 63)
        Vol. 28, No. 10; Vol. 29, No. 1; Vol. 29, No. 3
      - Atlanta Tribune, The (larger format), 1992-06-1999 (Box 56)
        Vol. 6 No. 3, Vol. 9, no. 11, no. 23; Vol. 10 no. 5; Vol 11 no. 5, no. 16; Vol. 12 no. 10, no. 12, no. 17; Vol. 13, no. 4, no. 6
      - Atlanta Tribune, The (magazine size), 2000-06-2015-06 (Box 43)
        Vol. 14, No. 3; Vol. 28, No. 9; Vol. 29, No. 1-3
      - Atlanta Voice, The, 2002-10-12-2002-10-18 (Box 43)
        Vol. 36 No. 16
      - AUC, 2006-10 (Box 63)
      - Audio, 1985-07-1986-02 (Box 43)
        Vol. 69 No. 7; Vol. 70 No. 2
      - Audio Services Corporation Production Sound Catalog, 1989 (Box 44)
      - Axcess, 1994 (Box 44)
        Vol. 1 Issue 2
      - B.E.T. Weekend, 1997-02-1999-08 (Box 44)
      - Back to One, 1998-03 (Box 44)
        Vol. 1 Issue 4
      - Backjumps, Undated (Box 44)
        No. 7, 8
        Largely in German
      - Backspin, 2002-10-2003-03 (Box 63)
        No. 38, 43
        In German
      - Beat (The Reggae and African Beat), 1984-1996 (Box 10)
        Vol. 3 No. 3-6; Vol. 4 No. 1, 3-6; Vol. 5 No. 3-5/6; Vol. 6 No. 1, 3-4; Vol. 7 No. 1, 4; Vol. 10 No. 2; Vol. 12 No. 1, Vol. 14 No. 1; Vol. 15 No. 4
        Volumes labelled starting 1986
      - Beat-Down: (Culture) for the Mind, Heart and Soul, 1994-1997 (Box 11)
        Vol. 2 No. 2, 4; Vol. 3 No. 1-3; Vol. 5 No. 5; Vol. 6 No. 1
        "Culture" in title starting Volume 3
      - Big Daddy, 2001 (Box 63)
        Issue 8
      - Billboard, 1984-1994 (Box 57)
        Vol. 96, nos. 50-51; Vol.97, no. 16; Vol. 98, no. 52; Vol. 100, no. 25-26, 30; Vol. 102, no. 11, 29; Vol. 104, no. 42; Vol. 105 no. 11; Vol. 106, no. 13
      - Billboard, 1995-2000 (Box 58)
        Vol. 107, no. 5; Vol. 109, no. 7; Vol. 110, no. 18, 23, 49; Vol. 111, no. 21, 23, 26; Vol 112. no 19, 21, 33
      - Birmingham Weekly, 2002-06-13-2002-06-20 (Box 58)
        Vol. 5, Issue 38
      - Black Beat Superstar Special: A Tribute to Malcom X, 1992 (Box 44)
        No. 8
      - Black Enterprise, 1982-07-2000-12 (Box 11)
        Vol. 12, No. 12; Vol. 15 No. 5; Vol. 25 No. 5; Vol. 26 No. 5; Vol. 28 No. 5; Vol. 31 No. 5
      - Black Enterprise, 2001-12-2011-12 (Box 11)
        Vol. 32 No. 5; Vol. 33 No. 8; Vol. 42 No. 5
      - Black Enterprise, 2014-09 (Box 44)
        Vol. 45 Issue 2
      - Black EOE Journal, 2005 (Box 44)
        Vol. 20 No. 4
      - Black Market, 1998-04 (Box 64)
      - Black Radio Exclusive, Fall 2005 (Box 11)
        Vol. 12 No. 35; Vol. 13 No. 27, 33, 47; Vol. 18 No. 38; Vol. 28 No. 3
      - Blaum!, 2000-2001-07 (Box 12)
        Issue 1, No Number
      - Blaum!, 2001-04 (Box 44)
        Premier Issue
      - Blaze, 1998 (Box 44)
      - BMI, 1992 (Box 44)
      - Broadcast Engineering, 1984-05 (Box 44)
        Vol. 26 No. 5
      - Bronner Bros. Atlanta Hair Show, Winter 1992 (Box 58)
      - Bronner Bros. International Hair Show, February 2007, August 2007 (Box 63)
      - C.I.N., 1996 (Box 59)
        Vol. 1
      - Caribbean Express, The, 1998-09 (Box 59)
        Vol. 2 No. 9
      - Caribbean Focus, 2000-01-2000-03 (Box 44)
        Vol. 8 No. 1
      - Cash Box - 2, 1972-09-09- (Box 59)
        Vol. XXIV no. 12. "Spotlight on Contemporary Black Radio"
      - CD-ROM, 1996-12 (Box 44)
        Vol. 9 No. 12
      - Center, The: 2009 Media Kit, 2009 (Box 44)
      - Champion Newspaper, The: Free Press, 2010-03-19 (Box 44)
        Vol 12 No. 51
      - Championship Golf, 2008-10 (Box 44)
      - Cineaste, 1980 (Box 44)
        Vol. 10 No. 3
      - Class, 1991-06 (Box 44)
        Vol. 12 No. 6
      - Club AUC, 2004-10 (Box 45)
      - Club Systems International, Summer 1980 (Box 12)
        Vol. 9 No. 5-6
      - Clubworld, 2008-07-2010 (Box 12)
        Vol. 10 No. 1, 7, 8; 2010 Collectors Issue
      - Coast 2 Coast, 2010-05 (Box 45)
      - Computer Pictures, Summer 2004 (Box 45)
        Vol. 12 No. 1
      - Concrete, 2006 (Box 64)
        Issue 11
      - Connex List, The, 2003-2005 (Box 64)
        Volume 13-14, 16-18, 21
      - Wonder Twinz, Forgotten Hip Hop Classics # 1, 2005; CD-2497 (Box 64)
        In The Connex List No. 18
      - Conscious, 2004 (Box 45)
      - Cool Kids, 2004-07 (Box 45)
      - Corner Store, 2009 (Box 45)
        Vol. 1 Issue 1
      - Cover Atlanta, 2003 (Box 64)
        Vol. 13
      - Creative Loafing, 1995-04-01-2015-06-17 (Box 59)
        Vol. 23, No. 45; Vol. 30 No. 11; Vol. 33 No. 12; Vol.?, No. 33; Vol. 44 no. 7
      - Cross Roads News, 2008-01-24-2015-03-14 (Box 45)
        Vol. 13 No. 37, Vol. 20 No. 46
      - Crossroads of South DeKalb County, 2000-05 (Box 45)
        Vol. 6 No. 1
      - Crunk, 2000 (Box 12)
      - Crunk, March/April 2005 (Box 12)
      - Crystal, 2003-05-2003-06 (Box 45)
      - CVC Report, 1994-12-01 (Box 59)
        Vol. 12, No. 21
      - Cypher Magazine, 1998 (Box 12)
        Vol. 1 Issue 4; Vol. 2 Issue 6
      - Da Buzz!, 1992-12-1997 (Box 12)
        December 1992/January 1993, Early 1995, 1997
      - Da Buzz! (large format), 1994-04-1994-05 (Box 59)
      - Da Real Deal, 2003-03-2003-06 (Box 12)
        Vol. 2 Issue 3; Vol. 2 Issue 6
      - Da Streetz, 2005-09 (Box 63)
        No. 10
      - Dance Issue Magazine, 1987-02-1988-12 (Box 12)
        Vol. 1 No. 4, 6, 8; Vol. 2 No. 3, 8-10, 12; Vol. 3 No. 2
      - Dance Music Guide (Trax), 1987-12 (Box 13)
        Vol. 3 Issue 22
      - Dance Music Report, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
        Vol. 9 Issue 14, 25; Vol. 10 Issue 3, 6, 12, 19, 21; Vol. 11 Issue 4, 13, 15
      - Dancehall Vibes, 1998-11-1998-12 (Box 64)
        Vol. 2 No. 11
      - Dapper, 2007-01-2007-02 (Box 45)
        Issue 1, Vol. 1
      - db, 1981-01 (Box 45)
        Vol. 1 No. 15
      - Decatur Dispatch, 2015-06 (Box 45)
        Vol. 25 No. 6
      - DeKalb Newcomers Guide, 2007-2008 (Box 45)
      - Digital Mix Magazine, 1996-07-1997-07 (Box 12)
        Alternate title" DX
      - DJ Times, 1994-03 (Box 59)
        Vol. 7 no. 3
      - DMA: Dance Music Authority, 1998-06 (Box 12)
        Vol. 6 Issue 6
      - Dollars and Sense, 1984-04-1984-05 (Box 45)
        Vol. 10 No. 2
      - Dollars and Sense, 1983-10-1983-11 (Box 63)
        Vol. 9, No. 4
      - Don Diva, 2001-2004 (Box 13)
        Vol. 3 Issue 10; Issue 17
      - Dope, 1999-03-1999-06 (Box 13)
        Vol. 1 No. 1; Vol. 2
      - Down Beat, 1984-06-1992-03 (Box 13)
        Vol. 51 No. 6; Vol 52 No. 1, 10; Vol. 58 No. 9, 11, 12; Vol. 59 No. 3
      - Down Magazine, 2005-08-2011 (Box 13)
        Issue 1-2, No Number
      - Down Magazine, 2006 (Box 63)
      - Downlow Magazine, Fall 2006 (Box 14)
        Vol. 2 No. 12, 13, 14; Vol. 4 No. 17, 19; Vol. 5 No. 20, 21, 22, 27, 30; Vol. 10 No. 16
      - Ebony, 2005-04 (Box 45)
        Vol. 60 No. 6
      - Economist, The, 2015-04-18-2015-04-24 (Box 45)
        Vol. 415 No. 8934
      - Electronic Musician, 1986-09 (Box 45)
      - Elemental, 1998-12-2001-02 (Box 14)
        December 1998, January/February 1999, May 1999, Vol. 1 No. 8 (July 1999); Vol. 2 No. 1, 3, 9; Vol. 3 No. 26, 27
        Volumes not numbered until July 1999
      - Elementary, 1996 (Box 14)
        Premiere Issue
      - Emerge, Summer 1996 (Box 14)
        Premier Issue, Vol. 2 Issue 6, 7, 8; Vol. 3 Issue 1, 8, 10
      - Emerge, 1992-10-1999-09 (Box 15)
        Vol. 4 Issue 1, 3, 4, 7-9; Vol. 5 No. 7, 9; Vol. 8 No. 4; Vol. 9 No. 3; Vol. 10 No. 3, 6, 10
      - Entertainment Entrepreneur, 2001-05 (Box 59)
      - Entertainment Weekly, 1990-11-2000 (Box 45)
        No. 38,No. 403, No. 540
        November 1990, October 31, 1997, Spring 2000
      - EQ, 1993-02-1994-03 (Box 15)
        Vol. 4 No. 1, 5; Vol. 5 No. 1-3
      - EQ, 1994-05-1999-06 (Box 16)
        Vol. 5 Issue 5, 6, 8, 10; Vol. 6 No. 2; Vol. 8 No. 6; Vol. 9 No. 1, 2, 5, 8; Vol. 10 No. 3, 6
      - EQ, 1999-12 (Box 17)
        Vol. 10 Issue 12
      - Excel, 1990 (Box 45)
      - Exclusive Hot New Music, 2004 (Box 64)
      - F.E.D.S., 1999 (Box 17)
        Vol. 3 Issue 10
      - Face, The, Spring 1990 (Box 46)
        No. 89, No. 99
      - Facilities Directory/Products and Services Resource Guide, 1996-01-1997-09 (Box 46)
      - Family Reunion: Homecoming Magazine (related to Howard University), 1976 (Box 46)
        Vol. 2
      - Felon, 2001-10-2002-01 (Box 46)
        Issue 1, 2
      - Fight Beat, 1984-12 (Box 46)
        Vol. 2 No. 1
      - Film and Video, 1996-08-1996-11 (Box 46)
        Vol. 13 Issue 8, 11
      - Final Call, The, 1990-04-12 (Box 59)
        Vol. 9, No. 7
      - Flavor, The, 1995-05 (Box 17)
        Issue 25
      - Flyer Promo Now, 2011-09 (Box 64)
        1st Edition
      - Focus on America, 1991-10-1991-12 (Box 46)
        Vol. 2 No. 4
      - Forbes, 1995-09-25-1999-03-22 (Box 46)
        Vol. 163 No. 6
      - Fortune, 1998-06-22 (Box 46)
        Vol. 137 No. 12
      - Foundation, 2008 (Box 46)
        Issue 6
      - Franchise Times, 2015-09 (Box 59)
      - Frank 151, 2004 (Box 64)
        Book 17 and 18
      - Frank 151 (atl), 1999-2000 (Box 64)
        Vol. 1 Issue 1, 4, 6
      - Freelance Forum Sourcebook, 2005 (Box 46)
        10th Anniversary issue
      - FreePress (The Champion Newspaper), 2007-11-30 (Box 46)
        Vol. 10 No. 35
      - Full Compass Catalog, 1998 (Box 48)
      - Gavin 24-7, Spring 1998 (Box 17)
        Issue 2029, 2286, 2287
      - Gavin Report, The, 1988-08-05 (Box 17)
        Issue 1718
      - Georgia Sentinel, 2000-08-30 (Box 48)
        Vol. 11 No. 1
      - Georgia Up and Coming, 2002-08 (Box 48)
      - Global Exchange: The Alumni Magazine of Atlanta International School, 2014 (Box 48)
        "Special Edition: 2013-2014 Annual Report"
      - Grand Royal, 1993 (Box 17)
        no issue #, Issue 4
      - Grid Magazine, September/October 2005, 2011 (Box 17)
        Premier Issue, no issue #
      - Grip, 2006- (Box 17)
        Vol. 1 Issue 4, Vol. 1 Issue 6
      - Grooveline, 2004-2005 (Box 17)
        2 issues (no #s)
      - Grooveline, 2003 (Box 59)
        2 Issues
        Newspaper. 1 Issue signed on verso of front page.
      - Ground Level, 1995-06-1995-12 (Box 17)
        Issue 13-15
      - GroundBreaking Entertainment Magazine, 2006-05-2006-06 (Box 48)
      - Guitar Player: Legends of Guitar, 1984 (Box 48)
        "1st Special Collector's Edition"
      - H.Y.P.E. Magazine, The, 1994-01 (Box 48)
      - HealthQuest, 1999-02-1999-04 (Box 48)
      - Hello ATL, 2005-03 (Box 64)
      - HHC: Hip-Hop Connection, 1992-12-1998-05 (Box 17)
        No. 47, 104, 113
      - Highpoint, 1994-02-18-1994-03-03 (Box 59)
        Vol. 2, No. 18
      - Hip Hop Encounter, 2002-2004 (Box 17)
        Issue 6, 6, 8, 10
      - Hip Hop Heads Magazine, 2003-07 (Box 17)
      - Hit! Magazine, 2002-2003 (Box 18)
        "Free! December Issue"
      - Holla!!, 2003 (Box 64)
        Vol. 1 Issue 11; Vol. 2 Issue 1-2; 1 unnumbered
      - Home and Studio Recording, 1988-08-1993-02 (Box 48)
        Vol. 1 No. 11, Vol. 2 No. 2, Vol. 3 No. 11, Vol. 4 No. 3, Vol. 5 No. 7, Vol. 6 No. 5
      - Hood Illustrated (Box 48)
        Issue 6, 8 (DJ Special Edition Vol. 1), 9
      - Hot Block, 2008 (Box 64)
      - Howard Magazine, Fall 2014, Spring 2015 (Box 48)
    - Titles I-O
      - Illtip, The, 2000-2003 (Box 18)
        Issue 34, 36, 40-42, 44, 45
      - Impact, 1989-02-27-1989-07-24 (Box 59)
        Edition 526, Vol. XI; Edition 527, Vol. XI; Edition 528, Vol. XI; Edition 529, Vol. XI; Edition 534, Vol. XI; Edition 538, Vol. XI; Edition 539, Vol. XI; Edition 545 Vol. XI
      - In Motion, 1991-03 (Box 48)
      - Independent Media Buyer's Guide, Undated (Box 59)
        Entrpreneur's Issue
      - Independent, The, 1980 (Box 49)
        Vol. 3 No. 7-8
      - IndieHype (IH), 2008 (Box 49)
      - Indulgence, 2002 (Box 49)
      - Industry Insider Magazine, 1998-2000 (Box 18)
        Issue 15, 19, 25
      - Insomniac, 1996-05-1998-05 (Box 18)
        Issue 1, 11, 17, 22
      - International Musician and Recording World, 1986-05 (Box 49)
        Vol. 8 No. 4
      - Intro, 2003-09-2003-10 (Box 64)
        No. 3
      - It's Official Magazine, 2006 (Box 49)
      - Jack the Rapper, 1981-09-16-1987-05-20 (Box 59)
        Vol. 6, Issue 283; Vol 6, Issue 298; Vol. 6, Issue 300; Vol. 7, Issue 313; Vol. 7, Issue 316; Vol. 7, Issue 320; Vol. 7, Issue 342; Vol. 7, Issue 343; Vol. 7, Issue 345; Vol. 7, Issue 346; Vol. 11, Issue 522; Vol. 11, Issue 553; Vol. 12, Issue 563; Vol. 12, Issue 565; Vol. 12, Issue 575; Vol. 12, Issue 576; Vol. 12, Issue 578; Vol. 12, Issue 579
      - Jamz The Magazine, 1998-8 (Box 59)
        Vol. 18 no. 8
      - Jazz Store, The, 2000 (Box 49)
        Vol. 23
      - Jazziz, 1984-09-1984-10 (Box 49)
        Vol. 1 No. 5
      - JazzTimes, 1995-04 (Box 49)
        Vol. 25 No. 3
      - JazzTimes, 2012-04 (Box 63)
        Vol. 42, No. 3
      - Jet, 2001-02-2008-02 (Box 64)
        Vol. 99 No. 11; Vol. 111 No. 14, 19; Vol. 113 No. 7
      - J's Rap Sheet, 2000-02 (Box 18)
      - Juice, The, 2004 (Box 49)
      - Juice: Sounds, Surf, and Skate, 2000-02-2000-03 (Box 59)
        Issue #48
      - Keyboard, 1982-07-1988-11 (Box 49)
        Vol. 8 No. 7, Vol. 12 No. 6 (Issue 122), Vol. 14 No. 11 (Issue 151)
      - King Magazine, 2003-09-2005-05 (Box 18)
        Issue 15 (May 2005)
      - King Magazine, 2005-06-2007-10 (Box 19)
        Issue 16-17
      - Kore, 2011 (Box 64)
        No. 3-4
      - Korg Professional Performance Series, The, 1988 (Box 49)
      - Latin Beat Magazine, 1994-02 (Box 49)
        Vol. 4 No. 1
      - Latin Percussion Inc., 1984 (Box 49)
      - Latin Style, 1997-10 (Box 49)
        Vol. 3 No. 5
      - Latin US, 1985-02 (Box 49)
      - Living Blues, 1980-1984 (Box 49)
        No. 45/46, 55, 56, 62
      - Living Blues, 2001-05-2001-06 (Box 63)
        Vol. 32, No. 3
      - Loaded, 2003 (Box 64)
      - LoMo Magazine, 2002-06 (Box 49)
      - Lowrider, 1994-01 (Box 49)
      - MAD, 1988-04 (Box 50)
        No. 278
      - Mainstream, 1994-08-10-1994-09-10 (Box 59)
        Vol. 1, Issue 10
      - Mandatory Business, Undated (Box 50)
        Volume 11: Atlanta Edition
      - Manny's Mailbox Music, Winter 1992/1993, Fall 1996 (Box 50)
        Issue 14 (Fall 1996)
      - MBE: Minority Business Entrepreneur, 1998-09-1998-10 (Box 50)
        Vol. 15 No. 5
      - Men Looking Ahead News Magazine, 2004 (Box 50)
      - Merchandise Unlimited Southeastern Independent Coalition (MUSIC) Directory, 2nd Quarter 2004 (Box 64)
        Vol. 5, 7
        Name changed from Merchandise Unlimited Independent Retailers Coalition (MUIRC)
      - Miami Kustoms Magazine, 2003 (Box 50)
        Issue 3
      - Mic Check, 1999-08 (Box 50)
      - Mic Check Magazine, 1999-08 (Box 19)
      - Middle East Magazine, The, 1984-03 (Box 50)
        No. 115
      - Mi-Life Magazine, 2004 (Box 50)
      - Mississippi Rap Report, 2003 (Box 59)
        Vol. 1, No. 4
      - Mix, 1980-1992-05 (Box 19)
        Vol. 4 No. 7, 8; Vol. 6 No. 12; Vol. 7 No. 3, 7; Vol. 11 No. 5; Vol. 12 No. 2; Vol. 15 No. 3, 6; Vol. 16 No. 4, 5
      - Mix, 1992-11-1995-09 (Box 20)